>> Brian: 请转至 " 详细信息 " 页面， >> Brian: And
&gt;&gt; Brian: So go to your Details page,
&gt;&gt; Brian: And
我们要从 ./CArosel 进口卡鲁塞尔
we're gonna import
Carousel from ./Carousel.
> > 布莱恩: 我们会把这个放在详细的页面上。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And we're going to
put this on the detail page.
它要走了，这是 .details 里面的第一个组件，就在这里。
It's going to go, it's the first component
inside of .details, so right here.
卡鲁索，然后在媒体上通过媒体，媒体。
Carousel, and just pass in media,
so media=media.
我们得把这个从国家的土地上拿走
And we have to grab
that out of this.state.
>> Brian: 因此，请将 Carousel 导入顶部，在第 27 行中，将介质从 this.state中取出。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So import Carousel at the top,
on line 27 grab media out of this.state.
然后，如果你还记得的话，这就是 API 的到来。
And then, again, this is coming
from the API, if you remember.
然后在 31 号线上
And then here, on line 31,
从 API中获取的介质 = 介质的 Carousel 组件中。
be out of the Carousel component with
media=media that we got from the API.
> > 布莱恩: 这应该足够了
&gt;&gt; Brian: And that should be enough,
现在你看你的页面时应该看到一个漂亮的卡鲁赛尔
now you should see a nice looking
Carousel when you go to your page.
所以让我们来看一看， >> 布莱恩: 噢，看那只小狗。
So let's go take a look,
&gt;&gt; Brian: Aw, look at that pup.
现在你可以点击这两个了，对吗 ?
And so now you can click on both of these,
right?
它会改变你所看到的图像。
And it'll change which
image you're looking at.
> > 布莱恩: 我只是想养那只狗，这就是我现在想做的。
&gt;&gt; Brian: I just wanna pet that dog,
that's all I wanna do right now.
>> 布莱恩: 我们已经到了另一个承诺点了。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Well, we have gotten
up to another Commit point here.
因此，我们现在已完成 " 添加详细信息 " 路由，添加定制 Babel 配置并添加 Carousel。
So we now have done add Details route, add
custom Babel config, and add the Carousel.
所以如果你在后面，可以自由地跳到这个 " 承诺 " 点。
So if you're behind,
feel free to jump up to this Commit point.